The skyline wakes up when the sun goes down.
A million electric eyes over the town.
Sun can't feel the hum in the floor. We're
leaving shadows right outside the door. Catch
the neon pole. Riding on the wire. Racing
through the streets. Glowing like fire. No
looking back. We're out of frame. Running on the
spark. Wild and untamed. Catch the neon pole.
The dashboard is glowing A steady bright green
The fastest escape that this city has seen
The rhythm is beating right under our feet A
steady transmission
out on the street Catch the neon pole Riding on
the wire Racing through the streets Glowing
like the fire No looking back, we're out of the
frame Burning on the spark, wild and untamed
Catch the neon pulse tonight
Through the tunnel of lights, blinded and fast
Everything broken's left in the past
Hold on to the wheel, steady and sure
We're chasing the frequency, perfect and pure
Catch the neon pulse Riding on the wire Racing
through the streets Glowing like fire No
looking back We're out of frame Running on the
spark Wild and untamed Catch the neon pulse
tonight
Wild and untamed
Catch the pulse tonight